<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>CVs on David Gallay</title><link>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/</link><description>Recent content in CVs on David Gallay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Certificats</title><link>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/certificats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/certificats/</guid><description>Certificats This page contains all my certificat in a downloadable version. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to look the rest of the website.
Cloud &amp;amp; Sysadmin Cloud Engineer Bootcamp Graduate Certified Kubernetes Administrator Containers Fundamentals DevOps and SRE Fundamentals: Implementing Continuous Delivery Essentials of Linux System Administration Kubernetes Fundamentals Linux Foundation Certified System Administrator Linux Networking and Administration Languages Cambridge English Level 1 Certificate in ESOL International (First) - FCE (estimated ~C1) Deutsch Zertifikat Formations (WIP) Bachelor in Cybersecurity of The School of Engineering and Management of Yverdon(VD - Switzerland), aka HEIG-VD High school maturity Diplom der 3 Orientierungsklasse</description></item><item><title>Skills</title><link>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/skills/</guid><description>Skills Languages French: Mother tongue English: B2 Cambridge certified (download) (~C1 estimated, not certified) German: B1 certified (download) (~B2 estimated, not certified). I would need a few days to get back on track. Italian: ~A2 Portuguese: Notions (A1 at most, able to understand easy speeches) Cybersecurity Engineer My CS Bachelor degree is about security. The skills I got and trained are:
Security risks awareness: What is dangerous and why Security mitigation: How to prevent/fix such risks Software/Malware/Cryptographic Analysis.</description></item><item><title>Odoo</title><link>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/odoo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/odoo/</guid><description>Odoo I work on Odoo since 2018. Odoo is a new generation ERP, aka &amp;ldquo;Enterprise resource planning&amp;rdquo;. It positions itself as a contestant of the famous SAP, leader in this field.
You will find my opinion on Odoo here
Open Source Odoo community edition is Open Source, this means anyone can read the code here. Nb: The code for the enterprise edition is also open source, but you need to have an enterprise license to gain access.</description></item><item><title>Open Net Sàrl</title><link>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/open-net/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/open-net/</guid><description>Open Net Sàrl Work on Odoo ERP (&amp;ldquo;Enterprise resource planning&amp;rdquo;), a contestant of the famous SAP Since 2018 Odoo gold partner: 1st partner in Switzerland, and 8th partner worldwide Roles, responsibilities and attributions Manage multiple projects, among the biggest one we have Great understanding of Odoo&amp;rsquo;s framework and its structure.
I often act as a Human &amp;ldquo;Source of Knowledge&amp;rdquo; for my colleagues. In charge of most of the technically challenging features, like optimizations or API development.</description></item><item><title>Career</title><link>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/career/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divad1196.github.io/online-blog/cv/career/</guid><description>German year (download certificat) Brig-glis (VS) 2010-2011 Goethe Certificate B1 (German) Highschool: LCC (&amp;ldquo;Lycée et Collège des Creusets&amp;rdquo;) (download certificat) Sion (VS) 2012-2016 First Certificate Cambridge Exam (FCE) B2 (English) Learned 1st year: Italian &amp;amp; Economics (only for the first year) 2nd year: Mathematics 3rd year: Biology &amp;amp; Chemistry (Specific Option) 4th year: Physics (Complementary Option) 5th year: No choice to make. Part of the rock band (Guitarist) for 1 year then the chores EPFL Lausanne (VD) 2016-2018 (Twice the first year) Formation: Physics It was a bit too hard for me.</description></item></channel></rss>